<resources>
    <string name="app_name">E-Summit</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="youth_summit_title">Youth Summit</string>
    <string name="youth_summit_tagline">First Flavour of Entrepreneurship</string>
    <string name="youth_summit_about">From the foot of the mountains to the very peak of the summit, Youth Summit ‘20 is your first taste of entrepreneurship — the story of a startup from scribbles on textbook margins to the gloss of Forbes. Covering stages from idea generation to application, the Youth Summit equips you with the repertoire an entrepreneur must have to traverse this trail with keynote addresses, startup case studies, a comedy night, failure talk and more — all tailored to a crowd 25 - 30 and younger.</string>
    <string name="innovators_summit_title">Innovator\'s Summit</string>
    <string name="innovators_summit_tagline">Marathon of Innovation</string>
    <string name="innovators_summit_about">Envisioned towards providing aspiring entrepreneurs with intensive mentoring and workshops from industry experts, Innovator’s Summit promises to be the one to nurture entrepreneurial mindsets and provide an opportunity to challenge oneself and to test one\'s capability in this marathon of innovation. The mission of the Summit is to empower aspiring entrepreneurs with groundbreaking ideas and collaborations to solve world challenges, uncover new possibilities and develop revolutionary ideas and solutions, catalyzing innovation.</string>
    <string name="startup_summit_title">Startup Summit</string>
    <string name="startup_summit_tagline">Catalysing the Growth</string>
    <string name="startup_summit_about">Aiming to prop the startup development, this two-day extravaganza is concentrated on providing networking and experimental learning. Designed as a platform for founders, investors and startup enthusiast providing extreme networking experience, ensuring you meet the right people, in the right business atmosphere. The Summit is crafted intrinsically for prospective and emerging startups looking for funding and expanding their network, service providers, business/industrial stalwarts, VC firms and Investors, and Incubators and Accelerators with quality sessions, workshops, seminars, round table sessions, panel discussions, pitch, and of course never-stopping networking.</string>
    <string name="techno_summit_title">TES</string>
    <string name="techno_summit_tagline">Riding the next wave of Innovation</string>
    <string name="techno_summit_about">E-Cell, IIT Madras brings to you its newest addition, the Techno-Entrepreneurial Summit, bringing out the latest and the most innovative trends in the entrepreneurial ecosystem. Aimed at establishing new horizons, the 2020 edition takes a dive into Blockchain, hailed as one of the most disruptive technologies of the decade. A highly versatile ledger system, finding usage in a multitude of industries is truly an intriguing domain for startup enthusiasts to venture into.</string>
    <string name="faq_q1">Will accommodation be provided during E-Summit in IIT Madras?</string>
    <string name="faq_a1">Participants will have to arrange for accommodation on their own during the 3-day E–Summit.</string>
    <string name="faq_q2">Do I need a team to participate?</string>
    <string name="faq_a2">For team based events, we will group you up if required</string>
    <string name="faq_q3">Is it necessary to attend all the events during E-Summit?</string>
    <string name="faq_a3">Participants are highly encouraged to benefit by participating in all the events and will be entitled with certificate of participation for the same.</string>
    <string name="faq_q4">Do we need to pay additional amount for E-shows?</string>
    <string name="faq_a4">The E-Shows are absolutely free for Youth Summit participants.</string>
    <string name="faq_q5">Is \'Case with peace\' a competition or workshop?</string>
    <string name="faq_a5">Case with Pace is a platform to share and solve pressing problems faced by start-ups through a workshop approach.</string>
    <string name="faq_q6">Are personal vehicles allowed inside the campus?</string>
    <string name="faq_a6">No. But you can use bus service available inside the campus.</string>
    <string name="faq_q7">Where would I get accommodation?</string>
    <string name="faq_a7">Participants will be given discounts in OYO room for accommodation.</string>
    <string name="faq_q8">Will I be receiving a hard copy of my certificate of participation?</string>
    <string name="faq_a8">No, we will be sending a soft copy of the certification via e-mail.</string>
    <string name="youth_contact_name">Ayush Toshniwal</string>
    <string name="youth_contact_number">+91 8975051167</string>
    <string name="innovator_contact_name">Abhishek Tigga</string>
    <string name="innovator_contact_number">+91 8290993926</string>
    <string name="startup_contact_name">Akshit Bagde</string>
    <string name="startup_contact_number">+91 7228901202</string>
    <string name="techno_contact_name">Charishma</string>
    <string name="techno_contact_number">+91 9840891737</string>
</resources>
